let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Warli painting is indigenous to which State?",
    answer: "Maharashtra",
    options: [
      "Maharashtra",
      "Odisha",
      "Rajasthan",
      "Gujarat"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Japanese art of paper folding is known as ",
    answer: "Origami",
    options: [
      "Haiku",
      "Origami",
      "Ikebana",
      "Karaoke"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Raja Ravi Varma was a famous –",
    answer: "Painter",
    options: [
      "Musician",
      "Singer",
      "Physician",
      "Painter"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is/are the example of cave paintings?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Ajanta Caves",

      "Armamalai Cave",
      
      "Badami Cave Temples",
      
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The colors known as primary colors are",
    answer: "red, green and blue",
    options: [
      "red and green",
      "red, yellow and green",
      "red, blue and orange",
      "red, green and blue"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who of the following is/was not a painter?",
    answer: "Ramkinkar Baiz",
    options: [
      "Tyeb Mehta",
      "Ramkinkar Baiz",
      "Syed Haider Raza",
      "Jamini Roy"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What was the subject of the earliest known paintings?",
    answer: "Animals",
    options: [
      "Animals",
      "Sports",
      " Flowers",
      "Landscapes"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " ‘Madhubani’ a style of folk paintings, is popular in which of the following states in India?",
    answer: "Bihar",
    options: [
      "Rajasthan",
      "West Bengal",
      "Bihar",
      "Madhya Pradesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The technique of mural painting executed upon freshly laid lime plaster is known as ",
    answer: "Fresco",
    options: [
      "Fresco",
      "Gouache",
      "Tempera",
      "Cubism"
    ]
  },{
    numb: 10,
    question: "Blue is an example of this element:",
    answer: "color",
    options: [
      "texture",
      "color",
      "contrast",
      "value"
    ]
  }
  
];
